准备好了吗 查莉
Ready, Charlie?
我们来让盖比瞧瞧你学会了什么
Let's show Gabe what you've learned.
-好啊  -那我们开始
- Okay. - Okay.
-"上"的反义词是什么  -"下"
- What's the opposite of up? - Down.
答对了
Yeah.
-"大"的反义词是什么  -"小"
-What's the opposite of big? - Little.
-那么"好"的反义词呢  -"盖比"
- What's the opposite of good? - Gabe.
这是奖给你的小饼干
And here is your cookie.
泰迪  你再过两年就要离开这个家了
Teddy, you'll be out of the house in two years.
到那时候可就只剩下你和我了
Then it's just you and me.
谢谢你送我回来  弗兰
Thanks for the ride home, Fran.
需要我明天来接你吗
Should I pick you up tomorrow?
不用了  明天不工作
Nope, not working tomorrow.
我可得为医院盛大的演出做准备了
Gotta get ready for the big hospital benefit.
你是知道我的
You know me,
我可是每年都赢得才艺表演冠军的弗兰·卡尔佩珀
Fran win-the-talent-show- every-year culpepper.
大部分时间我们只叫你弗兰...
Mostly we just call you Fran...
和其他一些不能说的秘密
And some other things.
今年我要和我们卡尔佩珀家族一起登台表演
This year I'll be sharing the stage with all the culpeppers.
我们是一个超级棒的才艺家庭
We're a wonderfully talented family.
我猜你们家肯定又要做观众了吧
And I assume your family will be in the audience again?
事实上  弗兰  这次大赛我们家也会参与表演
Actually, Fran, my family will also be performing.
-我们要吗  -没错  我们要
- We will? - Yes, we will.
好吧  但愿最好的家庭获胜
Well, may the best family win.
那也是我们的计划  弗兰
That's our plan, Fran.
好了  邓肯家族  把你们的屁股都挪到这里来
All right, Duncans, get your butts in here now!
噢  我可爱老婆的声音是如此甜美
Oh, the sweet sound of my lovely bride's voice.
我有个好消息
I have great news.
我们整个邓肯家族将参与到
The entire Duncan family is going to compete
今年的医院才艺比拼中来
in this year's hospital talent show.
很酷  那么好消息是什么
Cool. What's the great news?
你们大家别这样  我们怎么能输呢
Come on, you guys, how can we lose?
我们可是有世界上最完美的小孩啊
We have the world's most perfect baby.
我是指看看那张脸  你的脸怎么了
I mean look at that face. What happened to your face?
我不知道  妈妈
I don't know, mom.
我想我会很忙的  呃   总之晚上我会被破事缠身的
I think I'm busy, uh, whatever night the stupid thing is.
-对  我也是  -哦  真的吗  你们就那么忙
- Yeah, me too. - Oh really, you guys are too busy?
好吧  我跟你们提过吗  如果赢了大奖是
Well, did I happen to mention that the grand prize
超级无敌冒险岛两日游
is a two-day pass to super adventure land?
超级无敌冒险岛
Super adventure land?
-地球上最好玩的地方  -弗兰家必输
- The funnest place on earth? - Fran's going down.
弗兰家必输
Fran's going down.
弗兰家必...
Fran's going d...
我忘了拿我的钥匙了
Forgot my keys.
-你会度过一个很棒的夜晚的  弗兰  -好的
- You have a great evening, Fran. - Okay.
弗兰家必输
Fran's going down.
生活搞得一团糟
Day's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad says
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
■
翻译： kathyAR
就在这里  我们的家
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
■
校订： line
所以听取我的建议
So just take my advice
宝贝  不要放弃  世界有很多疯狂无奈
Hang in there, baby, things are crazy
■
后期： Johnny-Z
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第二季第八集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E08  The Singin' Dancin' Duncans
谢谢你陪我走到教室  雷雷
Thanks for walking me to class, ray-ray.
什么时候都行  艾艾
Anytime, I-I.
看起来你和雷蒙德处得挺不错的
So, looks like you're getting pretty cozy with Raymond.
雷雷  我是这么叫他的
Ray-ray. That's what I call him.
看来我和雷蒙德以后要经常呆在一起了
I'm gonna stick with Raymond.
哦  瞧他们两个
Aw, look at those two.
我们可以一起约会  如果你还和
We could be double-dating if you were still
斯宾塞在一起的话
going out with Spencer.
哦  你是指斯宾塞斯宾塞吗
Oh, you mean spence-spence?
嗨  今晚有个派对  希望你能来参加
Hi, having a party tonight. Hope you can make it.
嗨...
Hi...
嗨  今晚有个派对  希望你能来参加
Hi, having a party tonight. Hope you can make it.
看起来
Something tells me
丽奈特不想让我参加她的派对
Lynette doesn't want me at her party.
好吧  如果她不邀请我最好的朋友
Well, if she doesn't want my best friend,
那么我是不会去的
she's not getting me.
我也不去
Or me.
这种感觉似曾相识
That's kind of where we started.
好了  同学们
Okay, class.
这正值一年中最令人兴奋的时段
This is a very exciting time of year...
模拟法庭
Mock court.
我们将通过自己的亲身实践
We're going to learn how our justice system works
来学习司法系统是如何运作的
by having our own trial right here in class.
-泰迪  你来做检察官  -太棒了
- Teddy, you'll be the prosecuting attorney. - Yes!
某个人要被打倒了  这个人将会是谁呢
Somebody's going down. Who's it gonna be?
丽奈特  你来做被告方
Lynette, you'll be the defendant.
正义永存
And the system works.
斯宾塞  你来做辩护律师
Spencer, you'll be the defense lawyer.
沃尔特  你来做法官
Walter, you'll be the judge.
太好了  我已经感受到了至高无上的权力
Yes! I can already taste the power.
我也许犯了个错误
That one might be a mistake.
艾薇  你来做目击证人
Ivy, you'll be the witness for the prosecution.
那么剩下的
And the rest of you
你们将组成陪审团
will make up the jury.
如果你们谁需要我帮忙  我就在桌子旁
If anyone needs me, I'll be at my desk
玩我的数独游戏
finishing my sudoku.
嘿  "法律顾问"
Hey, "Counselor."
我要警告你  我爸爸可是个律师
I gotta warn you, my dad's a lawyer,
所以我也许会有优势
so I might have an advantage.
哦  是啊  不过  我可一点儿也不担心
Oh yeah. No, I'm not worried.
-我爸爸是做杀虫工作的  -那意味着什么
- My dad's an exterminator. - What does that mean?
我将会像杀虫一样消灭你
I'm gonna crush you like a bug.
-嘿  你从哪儿弄来的人体模型  -我在网上买的
- Hey, where'd you get the dummy? - I bought it online.
-我没和你说话  -哈 哈 哈 哈 真好笑啊
- I wasn't talking to you. - Ha ha ha ha.
我要把他放在我车里
I'm gonna put him in my car.
这样我就可以在为咕唧炸鸡送外卖的时候
That way I can use the carpool lane
注：carpool lane只有在车上有两人及两人以上的时候车才可以在那里行驶
使用拼车车道了
when I'm making kwikki chikki deliveries.
这么说人们就能快点拿到丰硕肥美的炸鸡了
So people can get their crummy chicken quicker?
没错  这对每个人都有好处
Right. Everybody wins.
当然  除了那些吃炸鸡的家伙
Well, except the people who eat the chicken.
还有那些炸鸡
And the chickens.
我想我才是那个真正获益的人
I guess I'm the only one who really wins.
你知道吗  我有个主意
You know, I'm getting an idea here.
你从网上买了这破烂  对吗
You bought this piece of junk online, right?
你在和谁说话
Who are you talking to?
现在我在和你讲话
I'm talking to you now.
噢  没错  我在网上买了他
Oh, yeah yeah, I bought him online.
那么  或许也会有别人想买我们的破烂
Well, maybe there's people out there who wanna buy our junk.
没听懂
Not following you.
我是说  如果有人笨的可以去买人体模型
I'm saying if there's people stupid enough to buy dummies,
那么或许他们也会来买我们不要的东西
maybe they're stupid enough to buy our crummy stuff.
-还是在和我说话吗  -噢  真是没救了
- Still talking to me? - Ugh.
现在  温茨小姐  请告诉法庭接下来发生了什么
Now, miss wentz, please tell the court what happened next.
-我的雷雷用七个感叹号来表示非常想我
- My ray-ray misses me with seven exclamation points.
艾薇  注意力集中
Ivy, focus.
嗯  雷雷说我今天看起来非常性感
Mm, ray-ray says I look hot today,
但这次他只用了六个感叹号
but only with six exclamation points.
-我该为这发愁吗  -说正事  好了
- Should I be worried? - Moving on. Okay.
现在我们来谈谈你在台上要穿些什么
Now let's talk about what you're going to wear on the stand.
你可别穿得过于闪亮
You don't want to be too flashy.
小泰  你看过我的衣橱
T, you've seen my closet.
大部分都是斑马条纹和豹纹的衣服
It's mostly zebra stripes and leopard print.
那些还都是我去教堂穿的衣服呢
And those are my church clothes.
那好吧  其实  你可以去翻翻
Okay, well, then you're gonna have to go through
-你妈妈的衣橱  -什么
- your mom's closet. - What?
你想要我穿着我妈妈的衣服去学校吗
You want me to wear my mom's clothes to school?
-对啊  -还在我男朋友面前
- Mm-hmm. - In front of my boyfriend?
我曾经做过这样的梦  可是结局并不好
I've had this dream. It did not end well.
艾薇  就为了一天而已  你可以穿得俭朴一点的
Ivy, for one day you can tone it down.
然后剩下的时间  爱穿什么穿什么
Then you have the rest of the school year
穿成和动物一样也没关系
to dress like the animal of your choice.
噢  挺晚了  我要走了
Oh, it's getting late. I gotta go.
今天是我爸爸的生日
It's my dad's birthday.
不好意思  还有一件事
Oh sorry, one more thing.
你明天在法庭上的时候  得表现得非常严肃
When you're on the stand tomorrow, you have to be very serious.
-如果能流点眼泪那就再好不过了  -别担心
- It wouldn't hurt to cry a little. - Don't worry.
如果我穿着我妈妈的衣服  我就必哭无疑了
If I'm wearing my mom's clothes, I'll be crying.
好了  现在轮到我们出场了
Okay, this is our number for the show.
PJ  放音乐
P.J., hit it.
我们是能歌善舞的邓肯一家
We're the singin' dancin' Duncans
我们是多么快乐的一家人
quite a happy bunch
我们总是在一起相互扶持
we will always work together
早餐  晚餐和午餐
breakfast, din and lunch
你总能看到我们灿烂的笑容
you will always see us smiling
夜晚  午后  和早晨
evening, noon and morn
我们像往常一样开始新的一天
we all start our day the very same way
当查莉吹响她的喇叭的时候
when Charlie blows her horn.
然后查莉就吹响了她的喇叭  你们觉得怎么样
And Charlie blows her horn.  What do you think?
奖励是无敌冒险岛两日游  对吗
It's a two-day pass to super adventure land, right?
非常正确
That is correct.
好了  现在我要开始
Okay, now I'm going to
向你们展示舞步了  你们跟着我一起跳
show you the dance that goes along with it.
开始我们的第一步  非常非常的简单
The first move... very simple.
我称它为轧轧步  就是要表现得像火车那样
I call it the chug, kind of like what a train does.
一  二  三  再来  一  二  三
A-one, two, three. A-one, two, three.
再来  一  二  三
And a-one, two, three.
好了  你们大家站成一排  都动起来
Okay, you guys line up and you do it.
-爸爸站在最前面  -好的
- Daddy in front. - All right.
-PJ  泰迪  盖比  -好的  来了
- P.J., Teddy, Gabe. - Okay.
-我猜爸爸是火车头  -希望如此
- I guess dad's the engine. - I hope so.
如果他是车尾  那这火车可开不了多远
If he's the caboose, this train's not getting very far.
火车头可是有耳朵的   孩子们
The engine has ears, guys...
而且还有感情
And feelings.
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
五  六  七  八
A-five, six, seven, eight.
一  二  三  再来  一  二  三
And one, two, three. And one, two, three.
-那个...  亲爱的  你的脚没有在动  -对不起
- And... honey, you're not moving your feet. - Sorry.
现在你的手又不在动了
Okay, now you're not moving your arms.
亲爱的  这学起来很难
Honey, this is hard.
老爸  这就像是拍拍你的头  动动你的胃
Dad, it's just like patting your head and rubbing your stomach.
这肯定会让你感到自卑吧
That must be really depressing for you.
好的  现在来假设我们的火车
Okay, let's assume we got the train
进站了
into the station somehow.
接下来的部分呢有一点复杂
Okay, this next part is a little tricky,
所以都看仔细了
so watch carefully.
我要开始做分步动作了  准备好了吗
I'm gonna break it down. Ready?
五  六  七  八
Five, six, seven, eight.
踏  点  连接着细碎的舞步
Touch, step, pas de bourree.
踢  点  大回旋
Kick, step, together, front and passe.
转向  定住  亮相
Turn, wait, ba-bam!
现在我们要奔放一点了
Now we're gonna sass it up a bit.
耸耸肩  点点地
A-shoulder shoulder, tap tap.
转个圈  用用力
Turn around and uh uh.
伸展  伸展  再来伸展
And whammy, and whammy, and whammy.
好了  现在我想要你们来做刚才我做的动作
Okay, now I want you to do exactly what I just did.
开始啦  五  六  七  八
And a-five, six, seven, eight.
一  二...
One, two...
你们都在等什么
What are you waiting for?
台下十年功
10 years of dance lessons.
我真不敢相信我们竟然赚了那么多钱
I can't believe how much money we're making
就凭着在网上卖我们的破烂
selling our old junk online.
这可比从个小孩嘴里抢个糖容易多了
It's easier than taking candy from a baby.
我是指  我早该明白了
I mean, I should know.
以前我总是从查莉那里抢糖
I take candy from Charlie all the time.
这是...这些气泡纸是怎么回事
What's... what's with all the bubble wrap?
额  只是觉得很好玩
Uh... really fun to pop?
嘿  你们谁看到我的保龄球了
Hey, anybody seen my bowling ball?
你借给达布尼先生了
You loaned it to Mr. Dabney.
如果那样的话我会记得的
I think I would have remembered that.
你的记忆力开始退化了  老爸
You're starting to lose it, dad.
比如马上
I mean the next thing you know,
-你会忘了拖鞋放哪了  -没错
- you're not gonna remember where your slippers are. - Yeah.
我来想想  我的...对啊  我的拖鞋去哪儿了
Come to think of it, where... where are my slippers?
老弟  我们得小心点了
Dude, we gotta be more careful.
老爸迟早会发现少东西的
Sooner or later, dad's gonna know he's missing stuff.
-我对此可一点儿也不担心  -为什么
- I wouldn't worry about that. - Why not?
我刚刚把他的眼镜也给卖了
I just sold his glasses.
哦  不  这可真糟糕
Oh no, this is terrible.
我们却一点忙也帮不上  你说呢
And there's nothing we can do, you say?
谢谢你打电话给我  弗兰
Thanks for calling, Fran.
鲍伯  我真不敢相信
Bob, I can't believe this.
-演出取消了  -什么
- The benefit's been canceled. - What?
-但毕竟你和孩子们为这付出了不少努力  -哦  天哪
- And after all that work you and the kids did. - Oh man.
你知道吗
You know,
我现在转  定  亮这套亮相已经非常熟练了
I was getting pretty good at that turn, wait, bam!
-是亮相  -亮相
-Ba-bam. -Ba-bam.
亲爱的  你能把这消息告诉孩子们吗
Honey, could you tell the kids?
-我可没心情说  -好的  包在我身上
- I don't have the heart. - Yeah, sure thing.
我也没心情做饭了
I don't have the heart to cook dinner either.
没问题  我们出去吃
No problem. We go out.
好的  我们出去吃  你真好
Okay, we go out. You're so good.
难道他都相信了
He bought that, right?
这就是你想要的吗
Is this what you wanted?
-没错  这很好  -这可比
- Yeah, it's fine. - It'd better be.
一个小孩在公交车上喊我阿姨好多了
A kid on the bus called me ma'am.
嘿  你怎么昨晚没回我信息
Hey, how come you didn't text me back last night?
哦  我肯定是关机了
Oh, my phone must have been off.
对  这也是我想的
Right, yeah, that's what I figured.
-所以我就打电话到你家里了  -你打了吗
- And so I called your house. - You did?
是的  没错  我打了  可你不在家
Yes yes, I did. And you weren't there.
-我不在家吗  -不  你不在
- I wasn't? - No no, you weren't.
所以我接着就祝愿你爸爸生日快乐了
And so I wished your dad a Happy Birthday
可是他却说"我的生日已经过去六个月了"
and then he said, "My birthday's not for six months."
怎么还不上课
Is this class ever gonna start?
最近怎么样  艾薇
How are you doing, Ivy?
嘿  你好  丽奈特
Hey, Lynette.
额
Ugh.
你们从什么时候起开始那么友好了
Since when are you two so friendly?
你想说什么
What are you talking about?
不
No.
-不  你不能这样  -什么
- No, you didn't. - What?
你昨晚是去参加丽奈特的派对了
You went to Lynette's party last night.
-我没有  -哦  别和我说你没有
- Nuh-uh! - Oh, don't you nuh-uh me.
-我想和谁说没有就说没有  -没有
- I'll nuh-uh whoever I want to nuh-uh. - Nuh-uh!
好吧  那么如果你昨晚没去参加丽奈特的派对
Okay, so if you weren't at Lynette's party last night,
-那你去了哪儿呢  -这件事和你无关
- then where were you? - That is none of your business.
不  看着  这关我的事  因为你骗了我
No, see, it is my business because you lied to me.
这件事还没完
This is not over.
不可理喻
Unbelievable.
他们说政府机构好比无聊的班级
And they say government is a boring class.
他们说得对极了
They're right.
你的目击证人  法律顾问
Your witness, counselor.
温茨女士  请实话实说
Miss wentz, please tell us in your own words
你在二十三号下午看到了什么
what you observed on the afternoon of the 23rd.
好的  当时我正在银行里工作
Well, I was working at the bank,
在二号窗口做出纳  这时有个女士走了过来
teller window two, when a lady approached
同时还塞给我一张令我感到威胁的纸条
and slipped me a threatening note.
那么  你能在这个法庭上
Hmm. And do you see that person
看到那个人吗
here in this courtroom?
是的  她就在那里
Yeah. She's right there.
嗯
Hmm.
那么你最近还在哪儿看到她了
And have you seen this person anywhere else recently?
比方说在一个派对上
Like at a party?
一个我没受到邀请的派对
A party I wasn't invited to?
反对  这些和今天要讲的有什么关系
Objection. What does this have to do with anything?
我同意她讲的
I'll allow it
因为我同样没受到邀请
since I wasn't invited either.
现在  温茨小姐
Now, miss wentz,
你到底去没去丽奈特的派对呢
did you or did you not go to Lynette's party?
我不想回答这个
I don't want to answer that.
你必须回答  你可是立誓要在法庭上说真话的
You have to. You're under oath.
没有  我并没有去参加派对
No, I did not go to the party.
-既然这样  那么你去了哪儿  -我是出去了...
- Well, then where did you go? - I was out...
和斯宾塞出去了
With Spencer.
肃静
Order!
等等  所以...
Wait, so...
-难道你在和斯宾塞约会  -我抗议
- so you're dating Spencer? - I object!
-我抗议  -我也抗议
- I object. - Now I object.
我没和他约会
I'm not dating him.
我在和他约会
I'm dating him.
我收回我的抗议
I withdraw my objection,
-今晚见  亲爱的  -你懂的  雷雷
- see you tonight, baby. - You know it, ray-ray.
等等  那么你干嘛和我的前男友一起出去
Wait, so why were you out with my ex-boyfriend?
我是和雷蒙德出去了
I was hanging out with Raymond.
但他同时又想和斯宾塞一起出去
And he wanted to hang out with Spencer.
我是觉得这很奇怪  可我还是去了
I felt weird about it, but I went along.
我不告诉你是因为我知道你会不开心的
And I didn't tell you because I knew you wouldn't like it.
她为什么会不开心  你说过我们是朋友  对吗
Why wouldn't she like it? You said we're friends, right?
哦  拜托  每个人在他们分手过后都那么说
Oh please, everyone says that after they break up.
-那么我们不再是朋友了  -不  我们当然是朋友
- So we're not friends? - No, of course we are.
好吧  我糊涂了  我们到底是不是朋友
Okay, I'm confused. Are we friends or not?
如果我们是朋友  那你为什么听见我和艾薇出去会那么生气
If we are, then why are you mad that I was hanging out with Ivy?
不  我没有生气
No no, I'm not mad!
好吧  我生气是因为我...
Okay, I'm mad because I...
因为...
Well, because...
看啊  我可不是那个让你们审问的人
Look, I'm not the one on trial here.
让我们先休庭
Let's take a recess.
我把小木槌落在我的袍子里了
I lost the gavel in my robe.
刚才我从弗兰·卡尔佩珀那里
I just got a very interesting
接到一个非常有趣的电话
phone call from Fran Culpepper.
她想来确定你妈妈是否准备了充足的小饼干
She wanted to make sure your mom baked enough cookies
为今晚的义演活动
for tonight's benefit.
那真有趣
That is interesting.
这有什么有趣的
Why is that interesting?
因为如果像你妈妈说的那样  演出取消了
Because if the benefit was really cancelled, like your mom said,
那么弗兰·卡尔佩珀为什么还需要小饼干呢
why would Fran culpepper need cookies?
哦  我明白你在说什么了
Ah, I see where you're going with this.
妈妈做了饼干却没有告诉我们
Mom baked cookies and she didn't tell us.
额  你这是要去哪儿
Uh, going somewhere?
查莉不肯睡觉  所以我想我该带她出去兜兜风
Charlie can't sleep, so I thought I'd take her out for a drive.
是不是有点打扮得太过漂亮了
A little dolled up, aren't we?
谢谢
Thank you.
我总是想把我最好的一面展示出来
I always try to look my best.
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我能进来吗
Can I come in?
随便你
Whatever.
我给你带来了些东西
I got you something.
他的名字叫贝里·索伊
His name is Berry sowwy.
看到了吗  因为它是草莓
See, 'cause it's a strawberry
我是索伊...
and I'm sowwy...
非常·抱歉
Berry sowwy.
喔  看起来你很不好受
Wow, looks like you felt real bad...
哦  原来只有九十九美分
Oh, 99 cents bad.
事实上我是在公交车上找到的
Actually I found it on the bus.
-你能原谅我吗  -我不知道  我对你感到非常生气
- Do you forgive me? - Well, I don't know. I'm very mad at you.
好了  别生气了  我不喜欢这样
Well, stop being mad. I don't like it.
我知道  我也不喜欢这样
I know. I don't like it either.
我知道我搞砸了
I know I messed up.
我之前从没交过男朋友
It's just I've never had a boyfriend before.
我不知道该怎么做
I didn't know what to do.
听着  艾薇  总有那么一段时间
Look, Ivy, there are gonna be times
你有男朋友的时候我没有
when you have a boyfriend and I don't
或者我有男朋友的时候你没有
or when I have a boyfriend and you don't.
-我喜欢前面一种情况  -好吧
- I like it better the first way. - Okay.
但关键是因为我们是永远的好朋友
But the point is since we're best friends forever,
无论发生什么  我们都该坦诚相待
no matter what, we have to be honest with each other.
你说的太对了
You're so right.
从现在起  我保证我不会再骗你了
And from here on out, I promise to always be honest with you.
-我们和好了吗  -是的  我们和好了
- We good? - Yeah, we're good.
我们和好了
We're good.
-哦  那么审判我们赢了吗  -你说呢
- Oh, so did we win the trial? - What do you think?
检察官跑了  目击证人
The prosecutor ran out and the star witness
也忘了她本该说的话
forgot everything she was supposed to say.
-我们是个好组合  -对  没错
- We're a good team. - Oh yeah.
太好了
Oh yes.
现在  我们有请下一个上场的节目
And now, please welcome our next act:
能歌善舞的邓肯一家
The singin' dancin' Duncans!
嗨  大家好
Hi, everybody.
我叫艾米 邓肯
My name is Amy Duncan
很高兴为你们介绍
and I'd like for you to meet
我们幸福大家子的其他成员
the rest of my wonderful family:
我的丈夫鲍伯
My husband Bob,
我的儿子PJ
my son P.J.,
我们的女儿泰迪
our daughter Teddy...
嘿  你忘了我吗
Hey, did you forget about me?
谁能忘了我们的盖比呢
Who could forget about Gabe?
最后上场的  也是我们最可爱的  查莉
And last, and certainly the cutest, Charlie!
我们就是能歌善舞的邓肯一家
And together we're the singin' dancin' Duncans!
我们是能歌善舞的邓肯一家
We're the singin' dancin' Duncans
我们是多么快乐的一家人
quite a happy bunch
我们总是在一起相互扶持
we will always stick together
你总能看到我们的笑容
you will always see us smiling
夜晚  午后和早晨...
evening,  noon and morn...
嗨  大家好
Hi, guys.
我明白你们真的很生气很生气
Look, I know you're all probably really mad at me.
亲爱的  我们不再生气了
Oh, honey, we're not mad anymore.
真的吗
You're not?
拜托  我们可知道你的本性啊
Come on, we know how you are.
人无完人
Everybody has flaws.
我知道
I know.
我的不足是虽然我有很多
And mine is despite all my wonderful talents
已经挖掘出来的才艺
I have yet to be discovered.
好吧  你们能原谅我  我真的很开心
Well, I'm just so glad you've all forgiven me.
没错  并且随着"假冒家庭"这件事的发生
Yeah, of course. And as far as the whole fake-family thing goes,
我们完全适应了
we've completely moved on.
新鲜出炉的饼干来啦
Fresh-baked cookies made from scratch.
-这是谁  -我们的新妈妈
- Who's this? - Our new mom.
好吧  你们耍到我了
Okay, you got me.
假妈妈  你现在可以回家了
Fake mom, you can go home now.
不要  我们喜欢这个假妈妈
No way! We love fake mom.
-她做饭  打扫卫生  -她还换尿布
- She cooks. She cleans. - She even changes diapers.
尿布  真的吗
Diapers? Really?
欢迎来我们家
Ha, welcome to the family.
好了  查莉  这儿有个
Well, Charlie, if there's
你老姐我需要你明白的道理
one thing your big sis wants you to know,
那就是不管发生什么  都要说实话
it's that it's important to always tell the truth.
没错  不信不立  不诚不行
That's right, honesty is always the best policy.
-这可是大实话  -呃  孩子们
- True dat. Yep. - Uh, guys?
-怎么了  -烘干机去哪儿了
- Yep? - Where's the dryer?
-我告诉过你他们会发现的  -快走
- I told you they'd notice. - Just keep walking.
-嘿  老爸  他们遇上麻烦了吗  -哦  是的
- Hey, dad, are they in trouble? - Oh yeah.
你的哥哥们现在可需要一些好运了  查莉
Your brothers are gonna need some good luck, Charlie.
没错
True dat.
尊敬的法官  这个女人找别人来假扮她的家人
Your honor, this woman replaced her family
仅仅只是因为他们缺乏跳舞的节奏
just because they have no rhythm.
现在鉴于她这种恶劣的犯罪行为
Now given the horrible nature of this crime,
我请求陪审团给予她最严厉的惩罚
I request the maximum punishment.
我同意
And so do I.
你在干吗  你是我的律师啊
What are you doing? You're my attorney.
你还记得上次你逼我吃花椰菜吗
Do you remember that time you made me eat all my broccoli?
现在看谁笑到最后  哼哼
Who's laughing now? Huh.
尊敬的法官  我们已经做好准备听取陪审团的最终裁决了
Your honor, we are ready for the verdict.
你将如何裁决被告呢
How do you find the defendant?
罪名成立  妈妈
Guilty, mommy!